The whole world is on fire, but we didn't notice
整个世界都在燃烧，我们却浑然不觉
I'm walking on wires in the middle of it
而我正走在钢丝上，置身其中
Standing in your, standing in your coat
裹在你的，裹在你的外套里
I think it's not fair what you're doing to me
我觉得你这样对我，不公平
Stop dragging this out 'round the city, baby
别再绕着这座城把这事拖下去了，宝贝
Dancing in your, dancing in your coat
在你的外套里，翩翩起舞
I want to be more than friends for the week, yeah, yeah
这一周，我想和你不只是朋友，yeah，yeah
I want to be more than friends for the week
这一周，我想和你不只是朋友
And if you want, and if you like
只要你愿意，只要你喜欢
I won't make you read my mind
我不会让你去猜我的心思
I want you
我想要你
I want you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you
我想要你，你，你，你，你，你，你，你
So what are we gonna do?
那我们该怎么办呢？
I'm feeling tied up in the image of it
我被这幻象紧紧缠住
This fantasy can't hold a conversation
可这场幻想，连一句对话都撑不起
How ya feeling? I would like to go
你感觉如何？我想走了
Wanna walk me home?
想送我回家吗？
Gimme a look, gimme a sign, you want a muse, you need a siren
给我个眼神，给我个暗示，你想要缪斯，你需要塞壬
I'm calling to you
我在向你呼唤
Every sip, every sigh, hands on my hips, we're gonna fly
每一口啜饮，每一声轻叹，双手扶上我的腰，我们即将飞翔
It's a beautiful thing
这是件美好的事
I want you (Want you)
我想要你（想要你）
I want you
我想要你
I want you, you, you, you, you, you, you, you
我想要你，你，你，你，你，你，你，你
I wanna be more than friends for the week, yeah, yeah, yeah
这一周，我想和你不只是朋友，yeah，yeah，yeah
I wanna be more than friends for the week, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
这一周，我想和你不只是朋友，yeah，yeah，yeah，yeah